Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Zines and APAs
  - Xenofilkia
    - Xenofilkia #79, 1 October 2001; Notes: Yellow cover with pumpkinhead judge judging jack-o-lanterns Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #80, 1 December 2001; Notes: White cover with American Eagle and broken hearted singers. On the interior the date is given as November, not December Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #82, 1 March 2002; Notes: Green cover with alien and insectoid alien, the interior says March, 2002 Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #83, 1 June 2002; Notes: Orange cover with band from Argo playing for frog people Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #84, 1 August 2002; Notes: Yellow cover with musical top hat ejecting a tortoise and hare Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #85, 1 October 2002; Notes: Green cover with dragon, guitarist and a wizard Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #87, 1 February 2003; Notes: Yellow cover with bird legged, tentacled, humanoid with tennis racquet? Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #88, 1 April 2003; Notes: Yellow cover with cat and dog on piano, playing and singing Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #89, 1 June 2003; Notes: Green cover with abstract of a person singing and playing guitar Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #90, 1 August 2003; Notes: Pink cover with adventurers and a dog and cat around a table Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #91, 1 October 2003; Notes: Yellow cover with cat person drinking from a bottle, leaning against a wall Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #92, 1 December 2003; Notes: Green cover with maestro conducting daffodils Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #94, 1 April 2004; Notes: Green cover with wizard in robes Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #95, 1 June 2004; Notes: Yellow cover with ghosts and adventurers in battle Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #96, 1 August 2004; Notes: Blue cover with pegasus and guitarist Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #97, 1 October 2004; Notes: Orange cover with paper crane and guy with gong Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #98, 1 December 2004; Notes: Yellow cover with cartoon of blood mobile person Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #100, 1 April 2005; Notes: Pink cover, adventuring party encounters a furby Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #101, 1 June 2005; Notes: Orange cover with soldiers in formation Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #102, 1 August 2005; Notes: Yellow cover with cat with microscope Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #103, 1 October 2005; Notes: Orange cover with masked guitarist and skeleton standing on pumpkin with black cat Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #104, 1 December 2005; Notes: White color with penguins singing Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #105, 1 February 2006; Notes: Green cover with sorceror with staff Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #106, 1 April 2006; Notes: Yellow cover with siren with harp and ship in distance Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #107, 1 June 2006; Notes: Light blue cover with stars, musical notes and sun Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #108, 1 August 2006; Notes: Goldenrod cover with lion and cat in window looking at indigistinguishable planet or moon. Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #109, 1 October 2006; Notes: White cover with cats on a satelite with musical instruments Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #64, 1 April 1999; Notes: Pink cover with gairy and hummingbird at a liquid bird feeder Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #65, 1 June 1999; Notes: Goldenrod cover waltzing foxes in human clothes Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #66, 1 August 1999; Notes: Green cover with fish evolving into land dwellers Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #67, 1 October 1999; Notes: Yellow cover with person floating cloud castle over kid making standard sandcastle Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #68, 1 December 1999; Notes: Blue cover with Alien guitarist at open mike Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #69, 1 February 2000; Notes: Pink cover with "there goes the neighbourhood" cartoon of faries leaving because of construction of a Walmart Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #70, 1 April 2000; Notes: Green cover with a demon, or maybe a faun. Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #71, 1 June 2000; Notes: Pink cover with Xena joke Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #72, 1 August 2000; Notes: Yellow cover with person in blousy pants Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #73, 1 October 2000; Notes: Green cover with person riding a sea horse and fighting a hammerhead shark with a trident Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #74, 1 December 2000; Notes: Goldenrod cover with unicorn head Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Xenofilkia #124, 1 April 2009; Notes: Blue cover with angels guarding a cat from the rain with umbrellas Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #123, 1 February 2009; Notes: Yellow cover with harp, Tully and guitar in shopping cart Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #122, 1 December 2008; Notes: Blue cover with reindeer and snowman caroling Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #121, 1 October 2008; Notes: Yellow cover with fiddling cat Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #120, 1 August 2008; Notes: Orange cover with spaceman and cherub beating drum, celebrating 20 years of Xenofilkia Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #119, 1 June 2008; Notes: Green cover with mime with two masks holding a guitar in an archway Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #118, 1 April 2008; Notes: Pink cover with very small person in ball in clawed hand Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #117, 1 February 2008; Notes: Blue cover with telescope Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #116, 1 December 2007; Notes: Pink cover, musical conucopia Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #115, 1 October 2007; Notes: Green cover with owl Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #114, 1 August 2007; Notes: Orange cover with a chef playing a harp and a metal fork being a tuning fork Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 2 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #113, 1 June 2007; Notes: Yellow cover with birds and flowers Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #112, 1 April 2007; Notes: Blue cover with cat in a window looking at the earth Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #111, 1 February 2007; Notes: Pink cover with singing Mount Rushmore Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #110, 1 December 2006; Notes: Green cover with hockey player and figure skating guitarist Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #109, 1 October 2006; Notes: White cover with cats on a satelite with musical instruments Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #147, 1 February 2013; Notes: Blue cover with reindeer and snowman and guitarist in snow Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #146, 1 December 2012; Notes: Yellow cover with giant turkey hovering over two vegetable farmers with guitars as only defense. Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #29, 1 June 1993; Notes: Single page photocopied onto yellow paper, with Harvester, by Leslie Fish Origin:; Songsheet 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
      Songsheet
    - Flier for Xenofilkia, Notes: White flier, dates at least 20 years after the first publication, but no date is given Origin:; Flier 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
      Gold, Lee; Flier
    - Xenofilkia #153, 1 February 2014; Notes: White cover with vase and faces illusion and musical notes. Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #157, 1 October 2014; Notes: Blue cover with scale weighing earth and music Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #142, 1 April 2012; Notes: Blue cover with guitarist on cloud with dog and sun and birds Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #141, 1 February 2012; Notes: Orange cover with Santa with guitar and reindeer Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #140, 1 December 2011; Notes: White cover with musical notes snowing out of clouds onto trees Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #139, 1 October 2011; Notes: Blue cover with cats in a basket and three mice (two are computer mice) Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #138, 1 August 2011; Notes: Pirate flag pole with guitars a la maypole and a dog and cat Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #137, 1 June 2011; Notes: Orange cover with cute animals, balloons and moon Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #136, 1 April 2011; Notes: Green cover with guitarist and dog hiking the stairway to heaven Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #135, 1 February 2011; Notes: Pink cover with valentine snowman with guitar Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #134, 1 December 2010; Notes: Blue cover with Antarctic Summer Solistic Caroling with penguin Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #133, 1 October 2010; Notes: Orange cover with cat and skeleton doing an el kabong with a guitar around a cauldron Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #132, 1 August 2010; Notes: Green cover with children playing go fish with a fairy Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #131, 1 June 2010; Notes: Yellow cover with personification of the sun playing guitar Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #129, 1 February 2010; Notes: White cover with snowman playing guitar Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #128, 1 December 2009; Notes: Green cover with hummingbird and guitarist in a duel the death Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #127, 1 October 2009; Notes: Yellow cover with rhyming dog Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #126, 1 August 2009; Notes: Blue cover with cat harpist Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #125, 1 June 2009; Notes: Yellow cover with "Bagelpipe" Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #1, 1 October 1988; Notes: Blue cover with dragon with hexagon Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #2, 1 December 1988; Notes: Yellow cover with keyboard with cats meowing and people milling around Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #3, 1 February 1989; Notes: Pink cover with person with scimitar on a flying horse Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #4, 1 April 1989; Notes: Blue cover with aliens and mushrooms, inside it says March, 1989 Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #5, 1 June 1989; Notes: Pink cover with lizard person riding a feathered biped. Date inside says May, 1989 Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #6, 1 August 1989; Notes: Blue cover with Elfquest style elf Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #7, 1 October 1989; Notes: Pink cover with mysterious hooded figure and plant Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #8, 1 December 1989; Notes: Light pink cover with carousel hippogryph Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #9, 1 February 1990; Notes: Yellow cover with flying machine with a frog and winged person and operator, possible pyramid in back. Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #10, 1 April 1990; Notes: White cover with dark elf with sunshades with staff Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #11, 1 June 1990; Notes: Blue cover with tavern with wizards and frogs and bipedal mammals Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #12, 1 August 1990; Notes: Green cover with a dancer in flowing clothes with a two horned creature Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #13, 1 October 1990; Notes: Green cover with six-armed dancer Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #14, 1 December 1990; Notes: Blue cover with hooded person with alien/fantasy backdrop Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #15, 1 February 1991; Notes: Yellow cover with adventuring party with giant cats/gryphons? Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #16, 1 April 1991; Notes: Blue cover with warrior with eagle and long peacock ribbon Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #17, 1 June 1991; Notes: Pink cover with anthropomorphic jackel Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #18, 1 August 1991; Notes: Orange cover with Bugs Bunny in knight outfit riding a horse "Toon Knight" Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #19, 1 October 1991; Notes: Yellow cover with warrior with long braid and staff. Warrior has bird-like arms and hooves. Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #20, 1 December 1991; Notes: Yellow cover with thin person in crop top and suspenders with phoenix in the background. Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #21, 1 February 1992; Notes: Green cover with snake charmer who is a snake charming a human out of a basket Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #22, 1 April 1992; Notes: Orange cover with a insectoid rock star with guitar Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #23, 1 June 1992; Notes: Blue cover with sea monster Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #24, 1 August 1992; Notes: White cover with person riding a floating horse? Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #25, 1 October 1992; Notes: Yellow cover with teddy bear organist playing in a church Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #26, 1 December 1992; Notes: White cover with an Old Time Religion joke Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #27, 1 February 1993; Notes: Blue green cover mermaid Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #28, 1 April 1993; Notes: Pink cover with person with firelizard Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #29, 1 June 1993; Notes: Orange cover with furry cat person Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #30, 1 August 1993; Notes: Blue cover with mystical person with geometric tights Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #31, 1 October 1993; Notes: Blue cover with lion-tailed humanoid person Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #32, 1 December 1993; Notes: White cover with Llamas night joke (referencing the Mercedes Lackey song Lammas Night) Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #33, 1 February 1994; Notes: Pink cover with "Toyminator" Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #34, 1 April 1994; Notes: Blue cover with lizard playing guitar and wearing a beanie "Filkasaurus" Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #35, 1 June 1994; Notes: Yellow cover with web-footed onesie next to frog person who is staring. Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))
    - Xenofilkia #36, 1 August 1994; Notes: Pink cover with alien with beer and guitar Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/#indexes; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #15 (V))